<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>More Furniture (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.MoreFurniture</packageId>
  <author>Anonemous2, wofl</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/MoreFurniture</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter>
    <li>VanillaExpanded.VFECore</li>
    <li>spoonshortage.rimkea</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Anonemous2, wofls mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2018490850
and the Royalty patch
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2020784345

- Included the royalty patch, loaded if needed
- Rewrote the core and the royalty patches
- The mods dressers and endtables will link to any bed that the vanilla dresser and endtable links to
- The mods dressers and endtables will be added to any title-requirement that has the vanilla dresser and endtable

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/MoreFurniture][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
More Furniture is a small mod that adds about a dozen new items into Rimworld. It was created so you'd have more variety when choosing things to fill your colonist's rooms with. Originally created by Anonemous2, development continued by me. 

[strike]ROYALTY PATCH: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2020784345[/strike] 
No longer needed


[h1] Contains[/h1] 

Several End Tables
New Lights
A New Dresser
More Chairs
A modular Couch
A Tiny Table
Kichen/Bar Counters
A File Cabinet
Several New Plant Pots
Four New Carpet Colors to match the default beds

[h1] Compatibility[/h1] 

More Furniture can be safely added into existing saves, But all new items should be deleted before disabling the mod. Does not require any other mods to work, and it should be compatible with most other mods.

[u]Patches have been added to make the following mods fully compatible:[/u]
- Rimkea
- Vanilla Furniture Expanded

[strike]Royalty compatibility patch found here: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2020784345[/strike]
No longer needed

[h1] Translations[/h1] 

Currently supports translations into German, Polish, French, Chinese, and Russian, but if someone requests another language, I can add it in too. (Beware, translations were done with a online translator and maybe abit funky, If you want to help/or comment on a translations, use the Translations discussion.)

[h1] If you'd like to see something added in, feel free to make a suggestion. 

If you have any problems, please let me know in the comments.[/h1]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>